American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Address by the Hon. Harold L. Ickes, 1938; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 7, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Safety Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Safety Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1941; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Safety Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Violations of Safety Orders, 1941; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Minutes of Advisory Committee Meeting, 1942; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Box: 7, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Safety as Applied to Grinding Wheels, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Proposed General Specifications for Fire Alarm Signal System for Factory Buildings, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Author: Industrial Board
  - Item 3: First Report of the Safety and Welfare Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Tentative Rules for Surpressed Air Work to be Considered, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Investigation of the Dust Collecting Efficiency and Operation Characteristics of the Dust Exhaust System, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Author: Committee on Rock Drilling, Sand Blasting, and Rock Crushing
  - Item 6: Report No. 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: What Accident Analyses Show, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Author: E.J. Kreh
- Box: 7, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Program of the Third Annual Meeting, 1916; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Industrial Betterment through Motion Pictures, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Supplementary Report of Fatal Accident, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Report to the Bureau of Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Immediate Report of Industrial Accident, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Death Through Accidents, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Author: Albert W. Whitney
  - Item 7: The Automobile and Safety, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Author: Alfred H. Swayne
  - Item 8: Dangerous Tendencies Propaganda Refuted by Facts, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Author: Cornelius Cochrane
  - Item 9: Contributors to Volumes One and Two, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Protecting the Human Machine, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Centre and Walker Streets, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Program, 1918; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: House Enrolled Act No. 234, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Industrial Safety Organization, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Topics for Safety Meetings, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Stop Look Listen, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Box: 7, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: General Safety Orders, 1915; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: United States Geological Survey Press Bulletin, 1908; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Mine Safety Rules, 1915; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Tentative Quarry Safety Rules, 1918; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Tunnel Safety Rules, 1919; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Tentative Safety Rules for Gold Dredges, 1917; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Safety Regulations of the Oliver Iron Mining Company, 1912; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Report to the Governor and General Assembly, 1910; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Chapter 15, 1910; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: A Federal Mining Commission, 1912; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Author: John Randolph Haynes
- Box: 7, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: General Coal Mine Safety Orders, 1920; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: General Bituminous Coal Mine Safety Standards, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Effective Sealing of Abandoned Coal Mines Alleviates Drainage Problem, 1920; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Reports of Investigations Working for the Miner's Safety, 1921; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: Dorsey A. Lyon
  - Item 5: Reports of Investigations Miners' Field Day, 1921; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: D. Harrington
  - Item 6: Reports of Investigations National and International Mine-Rescue and First-Aid Meets, 1921; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: F.J. Bailey
  - Item 7: Use of Permissible Explosives Increasing, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Reports of Investigations The Economic Relation of Accidents and Preventable Diseases to the Coal-Mining Industry, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: Arthur L. Murray
  - Item 9: Reports of Investigations Mercury Poisoning, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: R.R. Sayers
  - Item 10: Reports of Investigations Reported Instances of Successful First-Aid Treatment, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: D.J. Parker
  - Item 11: Reports of Investigations The Tannic Acid Method for the Quantitative Determination of Carbon Monoxide in the Blood, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Reports of Investigations The Spring Canyon Mine Rescue Association, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: A.L. Murray and P.A. Surgeon
  - Item 13: Operating Regulations, 1923; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Reports of Investigations- Underground Hygiene and Sanitation, 1922; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: R.R. Sayers and P.A. Surgeon